# **Alexander Heffernan**

heffernan.alexander@icloud.com | 022 521 7700 | Silverstream, Wellington, 5019

# **Key skills**

- Adaptable & Flexible
- Friendly & sociable
- Hard working
- Creativity
- **Quick Learner**
- Reliable
- Teamwork
- Time management
- Verbal and written communication

#### **Education**

## **Bachelor of Engineering** (Honours) at Victoria **University of Wellington**

- · Majoring in Software Engineering
- Completed courses in Computer Science. Engineering, Mathematics, Cyber Security, and **Computer Graphics**
- A+ average & Deans list Undergraduate since 2023

#### NCEA (Levels 1, 2, and 3) achieved with excellence

Graduated 2022

#### Other

### St Patrick's College Silverstream Dux 2022

Also received the Michael King Memorial Cup and Service Award

#### Year 13 Leader in 2022

Mentored a class of year 9 students

## Summary

Pursuing a Bachelor of Engineering in Software Engineering at Victoria University of Wellington, I am a proactive learner with a strong passion for technology and design. Over nearly 2 years as a website administrator in a communications team, I've honed my skills in web content management, collaboration, and design aesthetics.

My dedication to continuous growth is evident through my academic pursuits and professional endeavors, emphasizing not only engineering principles but also a keen eye for innovative design. I bring a comprehensive understanding of both technical and design aspects, coupled with practical communication skills, aiming to contribute to technology-driven solutions with a fresh and creative perspective.

# Career history

## Website Administrator at the External Reporting Board (XRB)

Mar 2022 - Present Office Assistant Dec 2020 - Mar 2022

 Delivering effective and efficient communication planning, delivery, and content creation to support the Communication and Engagement Team deliver the XRB's Communication and Engagement Strategy.

#### **Key responsibilities**

- Maintaining the XRB's website
- Working with colleagues to publish their desired changes to the website
- Collecting metrics on a weekly basis for the XRB's website, LinkedIn page, MailChimp E-Newsletter campaigns, and YouTube channel

#### **Key achievements**

Involvement in the creation of the new XRB website, including its new design, structure, and content. By working with colleagues both internally and externally, a new website meeting the needs of all users was launched at the start of 2022.

#### Crew Member at McDonald's Silverstream

Dec 2022 - Apr 2023

I started at 20 hours per week, steadily increasing to over 40 hours weekly for two months. While at university, I transitioned to a casual role, successfully managing work alongside my studies.

References from previous employers and teachers available on request